(+91) 9119620847 Hyderabad, India hi@prashantkatiyar.com

Prashant Katiyar

Tech Entrepreneur | Product Manager

Portfolio: prashantkatiyar.com GitHub: prashantkatiyar9777 LinkedIn: prashant-milan-katiyar

Startup Founder with 3 years of experience building SaaS products in Developer Tools, Hiring, Web-3 and Retail Tech Startups, which generated over \$ 3.5 Million in revenue. I run a community of 1,20,000+ Developers, providing tools to show proof of work. I also raised \$ 150K (₹ 1.1 Cr) in Venture Capital for my startup in 2nd year of college, and got it acquired.

EXPERIENCE

Product Manager Mar 2024 – Present

Innovapptive Inc.

Hyderabad, India

- Led the 14-member Product & Engineering Team to develop the next version of the B2B SaaS offering, RACE 2.0.
- Integrated the CometLabs' product to the internal hiring tool within a month, reporting directly to the CEO.
- Prepared a year-long roadmap, Jira workflow initiated sprints, and three features ready to launch now.
- Played a key role in hiring QA, APMs and Engineers to streamline processes within the new product team.
- · Managed daily scrum, authored PRDs and Test Suites, prepared UI with designers, and organised Jira boards.
- Increased developers' productivity and overall sprint capacity to 90% using best practices in agile.
- Utilized market research, customer feedback, and insights from sales to prioritize product requirements and user stories.

Founder & Chief Product Officer

May 2021 - Feb 2024

CometLabs (Acquired by Innovapptive Inc.)

Hyderabad, India

- Led the development of a cloud-based IDE utilizing Generative AI for code analysis and project evaluations.
- Secured INR 1.1 Cr preseed funding, served a thriving community of 120K developers & 18,000 active users.
- Built product from UI design to MVP; later supervised an 11-member engineering team.
- Established partnerships with GitHub and Vercel for seamless integrations to enhance the developer experience.
- · Adopted Agile workflows & Sprint Planning using tools like Confluence, Jira, Notion, Miro, Trello, etc.
- Outperformed competitors: 40% speedier load, 25% better efficiency, and 20% less browser memory usage within 8 months.

Associate Product Manager

Dec 2020 - Sep 2021

Hapramp Studios

Gurgaon, India

- Headed Creator Studio division: launching 3 major updates & initiating 4 beta tests within a 5-month timeframe.
- Drafted PRDs for Binance Wallet & KYC integration, achieving 50K+ DAU and boosting GTV.
- Conducted A/B Testing to improve performance, amplifying ASPU by 37%, Token Sales by 42% while trimming TTV by 20%.
- Coordinated closely with a 13-member Tech & Design team to ensure timely project delivery.
- Explored new revenue models by introducing NFT Minting after analyzing Web3 Market, increased revenue by 12%.

Product Intern

May 2020 – Dec 2020

Moptra Infotech

Noida/Remote, India

- Collaborated with Devs to refine a supply chain tool, enhancing user satisfaction by 15%.
- Integrated Amplitude, Google Analytics & CRM with e-commerce platforms, grew engagement by 12%.
- Led design sprints, optimized JIRA product roadmaps, and crafted PRDs based on user feedback.
- Conducted A/B tests on the e-commerce platform, driving a 10% boost in user conversions.

SKILLS

Product Management Tools

Jira, Trello, Notion, Miro, Amplitude, Mixpanel, TestRail, Metabase, Google Analytics

Product Design Tools
Programming Languages
Framework Technologies
Core Competencies

Balsamiq, Lucid Charts, Figma, Canva, Retool SQL, C, C++, Javascript, Python, Bash

ReactJS, NextJS, Tailwind, AWS, NodeJs.

Product Strategy, Business Analysis, User Research, Community Building, Persona Creation, Wireframing, Mockups, PRD, Product Roadmap, Agile Methodology, Sprint Planning, TDD,

UAT, A/B Testing, Product Analytics, Success Metrics, KPIs

EDUCATION

B. Tech. (ECE), Indian Institute of Information Technology (IIIT), Guwahati

Apr 2023

Entrepreneurial Studies (Seed Spark), Stanford University Graduate School of Business

July 2023

ACTIVITIES

Top 30 Finalist - HYSEA 10X Product Awards & Expo, Hyderabad Top 5 Finalist - EO Global Student Entrepreneur Awards (GSEA), Goa & New Delhi Founder - IIITians Network: Community of 59500+ Developers from IITs, IIITs 2023

2023

2021 - 2022